My dear friend,
Dio's bone.
What's happening?
Where is the bone?
Where is his bone? Now tell me!
I feel the bone's presence
from the Ultra Security House Unit.
Then Jolyne got punished on purpose
so that she gets confined at
the Disciplinary Wing to find the bone!
Yes. But it's too reckless.
If I can obtain the bone first,
Pale Snake will come after me.
And with him,
my father's stolen memory disc
in his hand!
That small man…
I must find him.
He has the bone!
Is he hiding somewhere?
What if someone gets
that small man before I do?
I must obtain the bone
before I lose it again.
What happened here?
They are already done fighting.
And everyone in the Disciplinary Wing
is abnormally bloated.
It's a Stand.
How many other Stand Users were sent here?
Are they the ones who did this?
Just what exactly did they do?
No, one User only has one Stand.
These prisoners were defeated by
just one of these two guys.
How many other Stand Users were
sent to this Disciplinary Wing?
At the least, there is one more User
who manipulates others into fighting
by stimulating their minds.
Can you stand with that injury of yours?
That thread Stand of yours was
most fascinating.
Especially since it's impossible
to predict its next move.
Even more intriguing, though,
is your mental strength.
Despite the damage to your body,
I can sense the growth you've had
since the last battle.
When Pale Snake said he would send
four Stand Users, including myself,
I questioned his judgment for sending
such an excessive number of us.
But now, I understand him a little better.
Especially since he wishes
to finish you off completely.
I am Kenzou, 78 years old.
The secret to my longevity is
eight and a half hours of sleep a day
and my daily "urine therapy,"
with just one cup every morning.
The important thing is
to keep the habit going.
Have you heard of "urine therapy"?
If you want a fight, I won't back down.
American-style.
French-style.
Japanese-style.
Italian-style, specifically Naples.
Those are "fuck you" gestures
from around the globe.
I will start by telling
you the conclusion.
These prisoners drowned to death.
I drowned them,
so their bodies are bloated like that.
And it seems that
I won't be facing you just yet.
F.F.!
Shit.
He knew I was sneaking up
on him from the bloated bodies.
My preemptive strike failed.
Not only that, but that bloated corpse
got in the way of my F.F. gun.
Close call.
F.F., how did you get in here?
I made it in the nick of time.
Looks like you're in some deep shit.
I'll fill up your wounds in a second.
That man… who was he again?
Right, he was at Emporio's hideout
with Weather Forecast.
Before I heal you, Jolyne,
I'll take care of this geezer!
Southeast, 127 degrees,
30 minutes, and 20 seconds.
Their sweat…
It will drip.
Will they open their mouth?
Do you want to drown?
Drown?
I don't know what your plans are,
but I sure love water.
See if it works on me--
The time it takes for humans
to drown in water
is between five to seven minutes
for those who have been trained.
That's only if there's air
left in the lungs.
But let's say all the air is sucked out
from both lungs.
In this condition,
humans drown to death instantly
with a mere few drops of water!
I directly struck
your fourth cervical vertebra
by going through your throat.
It contains nerves
connected to your kidney.
The adrenal gland!
It produces bodily fluids that
lubricate the respiratory system
like oil does to an engine.
Even a few drops of water
will make you feel as if you are being
swallowed up in a giant wave!
I can't breathe!
Right now, I'm in the body
of an average human, Atroe.
This is bad, this body won't last!
F.F.!
Do you want to drown too?
Jolyne Cujoh!
I have you!
What are you?
Are you really human?
Don't stand.
Just observe them from here for now.
Shouldn't you be assessing
what kind of Stand User that geezer is?
The problem here is not that
he drowned those prisoners,
but that he dodged every bullet.
It may seem insignificant,
but how did he do that?
That's more dangerous, don't you think?
What brought you here?
Your name is Anastasia, right?
I love you.
I couldn't wait to be here with you.
Say what now?
That old man has been incarcerated
here for 40 years now.
He's an idiot who drinks his own piss.
I thought I hadn't seen him
at the male wing for a while,
but who would've guessed he was here?
Even worse, he now has a Stand.
In the autumn of 1969,
this geezer killed 34 people,
all young men and women.
His sentence is for 280 years.
Though he's old now, he was 37
when he received his sentence.
He was the self-proclaimed
founder of a cult.
His sect was so popular
that even Hollywood stars joined it.
However, his cult's activities
clashed with society,
so the police and the FBI intervened.
Cornered,
this geezer locked himself
and 34 of his followers
in an estate here in Florida.
He attempted to burn everyone to death.
Kenzou drugged every follower
and set the building on fire.
All the believers burned to death,
but the founder survived.
Strangely enough,
it so happened that
a part of the wall collapsed on him,
protecting him from the smoke and fire.
He was barely alive when he was rescued.
There's no doubt he intended to die.
What am I trying to say?
Who knows.
I can't say for myself.
Either way, Kenzou alone survived.
He cannot leave this prison,
but he wasn't put to death, either.
These are the facts surrounding this man.
I don't know what you are,
but I can tell your strongest power.
The secrets to your strength, yes.
I can clearly sense something else
other than blood
running through your veins.
Is that your Stand?
Or are you an entirely different being?
Those things do not change your weakness.
Your weak points and body structure
are the same as any other human,
including the blood flowing within you.
Do you want to drown again?
This time, you will not survive.
Southwest, 225 degrees, 0 minutes.
He made something appear
in his hands again.
What is that?
And what is his weird footwork for?
Let's see the direction of your dragon.
F.F., it's behind you!
Wrong.
It's useless, so stop attacking me!
STAND NAME: DRAKE'S DREAM
STAND MASTER: KENZOU
Wrong.
It's useless. So stop attacking me.
I said, your enemy is the geezer!
You don't listen, do you?
I don't pick sides.
Your attacks will only pass through me.
Face forward! You better watch out.
The geezer's coming for you!
I have no right to butt in.
Mind you, the geezer.
The geezer is your enemy.
This dragon!
Is this dragon's ability allowing
Kenzou to dodge my bullets?
And here he comes.
This speed…
Those don't seem like
punches from a 78-year-old.
Now I can enter the dragon.
What's going on?
What did he do to his own arm?
His arm flew behind F.F.'s head!
That was close.
But they blocked his attack
in their own weird way.
His arm disappeared
the moment he touched that dragon Stand.
Does it conceal
the direction of his next strike?
What is that dragon-like thing?
Does your arm fly off
when you touch that dragon?
You still punch like an
old geezer, though.
Wrong, F.F.
I can already see what will happen.
But no one else can predict it.
Don't say unnecessary things!
Stop your yapping.
You are supposed to stay neutral!
You're keeping it to yourself,
that's not fair!
Just tell them!
You opened your mouth.
F.F.!
Was that a coincidence just now?
That prisoner's glasses flew up
and stabbed F.F's face!
Unlucky direction.
I'm starting to understand it.
He's using feng shui.
There is a principle called feng shui
in East Asia.
Kenzou's footsteps pointing to
cardinal directions indicate it.
As if predetermined, he advances
his attacks from one direction.
Furthermore, the Stand in his hands…
Kenzou uses that dragon-like Stand
to choose his direction of attack.
Feng shui?
What's that?
Direction of attack?
Feng shui.
It's a divination method much like
tarot card reading and astrology,
except it's not fortune-telling.
According to Eastern philosophy,
there are natural forms of energy such as
wind energy and water energy
flowing through mountains and valleys.
The flow of such energy is used
to guide one's life.
For example, feng shui is used
to determine the luck found
in an area, house, and even a room.
If the land or house faces
an unlucky direction,
it is said to affect the wealth, health,
and fortune of those who live there.
In times of war,
an enemy castle's feng shui was read
to decide which direction to attack from
in order to make the enemy fall.
On the other hand,
temples were built at castles'
unlucky directions
to counteract bad fortune.
This provided
further protection to strongholds.
Not only that, but feng shui's philosophy
is even applied to human anatomy.
There's such thing as
assassination feng shui.
You can use feng shui to determine
the luckiest direction of attack
against a human.
Then, no matter how the opponent
tries to block the advances,
it is possible to approach the target
without letting them in on the offensive.
Thus, making the assassination easy.
In other words, the unlucky orientation.
Kenzou's Stand must rely
on this principle.
F.F. must fight against
the direction of worst luck.
That dragon Stand points to
the best direction for a killing blow.
When that geezer's attack
overlaps with the dragon's location,
F.F.'s fate is sealed.
Who would've thought that Kenzou
has mastered assassination feng shui
during his 40 years in prison,
manifesting it as his Stand ability!
Feng shui shows the direction
he should take.
The same concept applies for defending.
F.F. missed every shot.
That was the reason!
It's because feng shui
worked in his favor and protected him.
Is that right?
Undoubtedly.
When he has the dragon in his hands,
he can read his safest direction.
After moving to that area,
he then prepares to strike.
The dragon points to
the orientation best for killing.
F.F.!
It wasn't a coincidence that
the glasses hit you!
Don't let Kenzou move toward the dragon!
I don't really understand it,
but you must not
let Kenzou touch the dragon!
Look at that, Drake's Dream!
They figured out my trick
because of your blabbering!
Shut up, old freak.
I'm not your henchman!
Feng shui should be open to anyone.
But it's true that the old geezer
benefits most from me.
F.F., this area is your worst luck.
Just above your left ear.
This area is the worst weak point for you.
Your lucky color is yellow,
and pictures of goldfish bring you luck.
If you have any, that is.
F.F., he's behind you!
So you'll chop me, will you?
I don't even need to position
myself in the dragon's orientation.
His defensive stance is also an attack.
Must be derived from tai chi.
Your mouth is mine!
Another instance where
the defensive stance is also an attack.
You wench!
Using the dragon's orientation seems to be
the surest path to victory.
I made your hand overlap with the dragon!
It works the same as if I attack.
Your own arm will now hurt you!
My attack overlapped with
your orientation of death!
Bastard, what did you just do to me?
What did you do with my arm just now?
I just said it's the orientation
for worst luck.
That's the power of orientation for you.
I can't predict what happens next,
and if I were you,
I'd try to reduce the damage to a minimum.
F.F., get away from there!
The meteorites destroyed the supports!
The fan will fall on you!
Oh, the fan isn't your threat.
The boomerang is.
F.F.!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter